(Howard:)Let me take you someplace nice.
(Raj:)I do enjoy the La Brea Tar Pits.
Really? Now?
With the traffic and the parking? It--
(Howard:)Okay, fine. The Tar Pits. Let's go.
(Raj:)Oh, why can't I stay mad at you?
(Leonard:)-Yeah.
-Ha-ha-ha.
COMMENTATOR [ON TV]: Breaks tackle.
-Go, go.
COMMENTATOR: He breaks another.
-Go! Yes!
(Leonard:)Are you people watching this?
Is this amazing or what?
(Penny:)Sweetie, that's a highlight
from the '98 championship game.
Oh. Did not know that. Ha.
(Penny:)-How much beer have you had?
-None, why?
Oh. Just kind of hoping you were drunk.
(Penny:)-Now we're back live.
-Okay, yeah.
No, I can see the difference.
(Guy in baseball hat:)-That's intentional grounding.
-Totally.
(Leonard:)Yeah--
That completely was a forward pass...